Guide to the Robert Kraushaar papers, [ca. 1970-1990]
Kraushaar, Robert papers
- Jackson, Helen. Economic Development - The Structure of Activity. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, 1988., February 26, 1988; Document (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Distinguishes between the core and supporting activities of the Council in economic development. 5 pages
- [no author provided] Sheffield's Twin Valleys - A Strategy for Economic Regeneration. Sheffield, England: Department of Employment and Economic Development, 1987., July 1, 1987; Bound Document (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Outline of Twin Valley Programme. 12 pages
- Hayman, Keith. Memo: Community Business/Employment. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, 1984, September 13, 1984; Document (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Various documents about community enterprise developments. 11 pages
- Blunkett, David; Green, Geoff. Building From the Bottom: The Sheffield Experience. Sheffield, England: Building.WPD, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Analytical paper (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Paper on relationships among government, social policy, and economic climate. 27 pages
- [no author provided] Resource Plan for 1985/86. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, 1983., April 21, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Ouline of planned projects. 6 pages
- [no author provided] Industrial Rates in Sheffield. Sheffield, England: City Council, 1981., October 1, 1981; Document (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Rate and tax analysis on production. For the public. Diagrams. 4 pages
- [no author provided] Business Management Development Programme. Sheffield, England: City Council, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Public promotional pamphlet. 1 page
- [no author provided] Sheffield Development Office. Sheffield, England: Development Office, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Public pamphlet describing functions of office. 1 page
- [no author provided] The Monseco Advanced Dehumidifier. Sheffield, England: Mons Precision Services Ltd, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Promotional pamphlet. 1 page
- [no author provided] Sheffield Information Technology Centre. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Public pamphlet describing functions of centre. 1 page
- [no author provided] Sheffield Co-operative Development Group. Sheffield, England: Co-operative Development Group, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Pamphlet describing functions of a co-operative. 1 page
- [no author provided] Womens Technology Training Workshop. Sheffield, England: Employment Department, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Pamphlet describing the workshop. 1 page
- [no author provided] Want to be your own boss?.Sheffield, England: Employment Department, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Pamphlet of the Sheffield Ethnic Minorities Business Initiative. 1 page
- [no author provided] Enterprise Workshops. Sheffield, England: Department of Employment and Economic Development, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Pamphlet on business start-up assistance. 1 page
- [no author provided] Asbestos in the Home. Sheffield, England: City Council Housing Department, 1983., November 1, 1983; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Pamphlet on what the Council is doing about asbestos. 1 page
- [no author provided] Enforced Tendering - The Sheffield Approach. Sheffield, England: Departmnet of Employment and Economic Development, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Document (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Information Pack on the council's approach to controlling contratcs with industries to provide social services. 9 pages
- Blunkett, David. Bridge Across the Credibility Gap. Sheffield, England: Frontiers, The Employment Page, 1987., January 8, 1987; Newspaper article (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Article on the Labour Party's attempt to create jobs. 1 page
- Spencer, John. All Change Under the Betts Blueprint. Sheffield, England: Frontiers, The Employment, 1987., January 13, 1988; Newspaper article (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Article on new Town Hall leaders' work. 1 page
- multiple. Sheffield Partnership in Action.Sheffield, England: The Star Industrial Survey, 1988., January 13, 1988; Newspaper article (Box 2, Folder 18)
  City Council officers' reflections on partnership between business community and local authority. 1 page
- Strange, Ian. Participating in Partnership.Sheffield, England: Local Economy, 1996., August 1, 1996; Magazine article (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Article on the relationship between business and urban affairs. 14 pages
- [no author provided] Review of the work in the first year of the Employment Department. Sheffield, England: Employment Programme Committee, 1983., June 1, 1983; Document (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Detailed report on work. 80 pages
- [no author provided] Checking Private Building Contractors. Sheffield, England: Joint Works Group, 1983., February 1, 1983; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Methods, policies around checking building contractors. 22 pages
- [no author provided] Sheffield - Hallmark for the Future. Sheffield, England: [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Booklet (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Public booklet on Sheffield's plans. 15 pages
- [no author provided] Women in Sheffield - Women's Work and Childcare. Sheffield, England: City Council, 1983., c. 1983; Leaflet (Box 2, Folder 18)
- [no author provided] Women in Sheffield - Women's Work: Low Pay. Sheffield, England: City Council, 1983., c. 1983; Leaflet (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Clavel, Pierre. Progressive Movements in Great Britain., April 23, 1991; Course packet (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Course reserve: collection of Sheffield progressive policy articles for CRP 315
- RK. Benington's Writing - Thoughts on Structure. [no more information provided], October 16, ?; Notes (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Notes on Benington's writing. Handwritten. 1 page
- Kraushaar, Robert. List of Resource Papers on Sheffield, Uknown; Document (Box 2, Folder 21)
- various - put together by Kraushaar. List of UK Items - John Bennington Papers Acquired by Robert Kraushaar. Sheffield, England, 1991., February 1991; Document (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Benington, John. Local Government Becomes Big Business - Corporate Management and the Politics of Urban Problems. Sheffield, England, [no date provided, c. 1980], c. 1980; Document (Box 2, Folder 21)
  "Benington's Seminal Piece" - analytical paper including diagrams and charts of structure for local authorities and committees. 18 pages
- Parliamentary Spokesmans Working Group. Alternative Regional Strategy: A Framework for Discussion. London, UK: Parliamentary Spokesmans Working Group., September 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Pamphlet: 32 pages
- Parliamentary Spokesmans Working Group. Planning for Full Employment: Options for a Modern Employment Strategy. London, UK: Parliamentary Spokesmans Working Group., September 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Parliamentary Spokesmans Working Group. Real Needs - Local Jobs. London, UK: Parliamentary Spokesmans Working Group., January 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Benoy, Henry. "Discretionary Spending by Local Authorities" from Local Government Policy Making, March 1986, pp. 48-54, March 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Photocopy of journal article: 7 pages (2 copies)
- Crawford, Colin. "The Legal Aspects of Section 137 - Recent Developments". In Local Government Policy Making, March 1986, pp. 70-84., March 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Photocopy of journal article: 13 pages (2 copies)
- Pilgrim, Martin. "Section 137: An AMA Perspective". In Local Government Policy Making, March 1986, pp. 66-71. (missing p. 70), March 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Photocopy of journal article: 5 pages (2 copies)
- Coulson, Andrew & Game, Chris. "The Future of Section 137 Expenditure". In Local Government Policy Making, March 1986, pp. 42-47., March 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Photocopy of journal article: 6 pages (2 copies)
- Mollenkopf, John & Castells, Manuel. Dual City: Restructuring New York, October 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of chapters 12-Conclusion (pp.315-419)
- Travers, Tony. The Politics of Local Government Finance, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of chapter 8 "The 1979-83 Conservative Government" (pp.79-149)
- Smith, Michael. Cities in Transformation: Class, Capital, and the State, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of book
- Laclau, Ernesto & Mouffe, Chantal. Hegemony and Socialist Strategy: Towards a Radical Democratic Politics, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of chapter 4 "Hegemony and Radical Democracy" (pp.149-195)
- Martin, Ron. The Geography of De-Industrialization, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of chapter 8 "Thatcherism and Britain's Industrial Landscape" (pp.238-287)
- Young, Ken & Mason, Charlie. Urban Economic Development: New Roles and Relationships, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of chapter 5 "Organising for Economic Development: The Formulation of Local Authority Economic Policies in West Yorkshire" - John Mawson (pp.79-105)
- Clark, Norman & Juma, Calestous. Long-Run Economics: An Evolutionary Approach to Economic Growth, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of introduction (pp.3-20)
- Boddington, Stephen, et. al.. Developing the Socially Useful Economy, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Photocopy of chapter 6 "Restructuring Political Economy: Social Needs Versus the Needs of Capital" (pp.119-144)
- Various. Various papers/articles on the nature of community orgainizing structures in reference to Saul Alinsky, Various (Box 3, Folder 4)
  "Organizing Grassroots Power: Transcending Alinsky-Style Leadership" - David Campbell (1986)
- (Box 3, Folder 4)
  "The Myth of Saul Alinsky" - Frank Riessman (?)
- (Box 3, Folder 4)
  "The Recovery of the Neighbourhood - A New Balance of Power?" - Dr. Tony Gibson (1984)
- (Box 3, Folder 4)
  "Community Organizing in the 80s: Toward a Post-Alinsky Agenda" - John McKnight and John Kretzmann (1984)
- (Box 3, Folder 4)
  "Organizing for Neighborhood Development" - Robert Giloth (1985)
- Center for Local Economic Strategies (CLES). Various reports and pamphlets from the Center for Local Economic Strategies (CLES) 1986-1987, June 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Local Work (First Issue, 15 pages)
- 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Annual Report and Accounts 1986 (19 pages)
- May 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Economic Sense: Local Jobs Plan (42 pages)
- June 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Jobs for Black People (4 pages)
- October 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Enterprise Boards: Their Contribution to Economic Development and Investment (21 pages)
- November 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  The Roots of Urban Crisis - based on keynote address at CLES conference by Doreen Massey (13 pages)
- December 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  More than Just a Poll Tax: The Economic Impace of the Local Government Finance Bill (92 pages)
- 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  CLES information pamphlet (folder with loose handouts)
- Center for Local Economic Strategies (CLES). Various reports and pamphlets from the Center for Local Economic Strategies (CLES) 1988 - 1990, February 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Local Economic News: A Monthly Current Awareness Service on Local Economic Development (Issue No. 23, 14 pages)
- March 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Local Work (No. 7, 28 pages)
- March 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  "Urban Development Corporations: An Explanation" -prepared by John Darwin (6 pages)
- March 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  "Regenerating the Cities" - prepared by John Darwin (24+ pages)
- March 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  "Economic Development: The Role of Local Authorities" (39 pages)
- October 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Inner City Regeneration: A Local Authority Perspective - A First Year Report of the CLES Monitoring Project on Urban Development Corporations (97 pages)
- Various. Various papers/articles on Progressive Cities, Spring 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Journal of Planning Education and Research (Vol. 11, No. 3) full journal with article "The Establishment of the San Diego Housing Trust Fund: Lessons for Theory and Practice" - Nico Calavita and Kenneth Grimes
- April 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  "The Politics of Jobs in Maine" - Pierre Clavel and Karen Westmont (working paper, 31 pages)
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 7)
  "Socialism and the Housing Movement: Lessons from Boston" - Kathy McAfee (12 pages)
- July 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Annotated Bibliography on Progressive Cities - Pierre Clavel, et. al. (Draft, 50 pages)
- October 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  "City Planning and the Progressive City" - Pierre Clavel (presented at ACSP Annual Meeting, printout, 10 pages)
- November 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  "Community Development in the Progressive City: U.S. Cases" - Pierre Clavel (presented at the Conferene on Empowering Communities, Ruskin College, Oxford, UK: printout, 11 pages)
- Various. Various papers/articles on Chicago, Unknown (Box 3, Folder 8)
  "Public/Private Partnerships in the United States: From Growth Machines to Urban Populism" (1 pages)
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 8)
  "Spatial Change and Social Justice: Alternative Economic Development in Chicago" - Robert Giloth and Robert Mier (photocopy of article, 14 pages)
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 8)
  "Challenging Chicago's Growth Machine: A Preliminary Report on the Washington Administration" - Bennett, Squires, McCourt, Nyden (photocopy of article, 13 pages)
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 8)
  "The Chicago Growth Machine: Race, Class, and the Response to Urban Decline" - Bennett, Squires, McCourt, Nyden (copy of paper based on forthcoming book, 24 pages)
- Summer 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  "Lessons from Chicago: Linkages and Neighborhood Economic Development" - John Okun from New York Prospect (2 pages)
- August 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Chicago Works Together II: Recommended Changes to the 1984 Chicago Development Plan - Chicago Works Together Planning Task Force (36 pages)
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Synopsis of Chicago Works Together II (author unknown, photocopy, 11 pages)
- April 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  "Local Development Policy in Chicago: A Case of Progressive Reform?" - Kenneth Reardon (copy of paper presented at New York State Political Science Association Meetings, 29 pages)
- [no author]. Urban Struggles in Italy, [no date found] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Pamphlet (working paper): 14 pages
- Thomas, David N. [editor]. Community Work in the Eighties. London, UK: National Institute for Social Work., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Pamphlet: 100 pages
- Wiener, Ron. The Economic Base of Leeds. Leeds, UK: Workers Educational Association, [no date found] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Pamphlet: 21 pages
- The Leeds Political Economy Class. The Need to Change the Way We Live: The Social Base of Leeds. Leeds, UK: Leeds Workers Educational Association Branch., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Pamphlet: 24 pages
- Local Government Training Board. The Contribution of Local Government to Local Economic Development: A Discussion Document. Luton, UK: Local Government Training Board., [no date found] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Pamphlet: 22 pages
- Riessman, Frank, et.al. [editors]. Social Policy, vol. 15, no. 1, Summer 1984, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Journal publication: 64 pages
- Lawless, Paul. Public-Private Partnerships in the United Kingdom, December 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Working paper presented at conference on Public Private Sector Partnerships in Urban Redevelopment in Koln, Germany; December 1991; pamphlet format published by Sheffield City Polytechnic Centre for Regional Economic and Social Research: 54 pages
- [no author]. "A Public/Private Support System for Community-Based Organizations Involved in Economic Development in Pittsburgh", [no date found] (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Printout of working paper: 21 pages
- Economic Development Committee, West Midlands County Council. Action in the Local Economy, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Pamphlet: Progress Report published by West Midlands City Council: 36 pages
- Sheffield City Council Department of Employment and Economic Development. Building for our Future Needs: Homes and Jobs Conference Report, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Spiral-bound Pamphlet: published by Sheffield City Council: 65 pages
- The South East Economic Development Strategy (SEEDS) Association. The South-South Divide, May 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Pamphlet: published by SEEDS Association: 88 pages Inserts: South-South Divide summary pamphlet (2 pages); SEEDS information pamphlet (2 pages); SEEDS publication order form (2 pages)
- The Centre for Employment Initiatives. Various, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Initiatives (Journal of the Centre for Employment Initiatives) - Vol. 3, No. 5, October; Vol 3, No. 6, December (27 pages each)
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  "Technical Assistance Research and Development Information: For People and Organisations Concerned with Combating Unemployment and Promiting Economic Development" (pamphlet)
- April 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  "A Manpower Initiative for Inverclyde: Why, How and at what Cost?" (copy of paper, 71 pages)
- Manchester City Council. WORK! A Strategy for Employment, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Pamphlet, pages
- Various, Oxford University Press. Community Development Journal: An International Forum, October 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Journal, Volume 21, No. 4
- Kraushaar, Robert. Dilemmas of Radical Reform: Great Britain's Community Development Project, March 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Bound copy of book (190 pages)
- Various. Various Articles/Clippings, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Originals and Photocopies
- Cooke, Phillip. "Battered Defences, Tattered Turf", May 21, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Photocopy of article from May 21, 1986 issue of The Times Higher Education Supplement: 1 page
- Cooke, Phillip. "Britain Goes on a Bender", May 28, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Photocopy of article from May 28, 1986 issue of The Times Higher Education Supplement: 1 page
- [no author]. "GLC Staff Pension Fund's 1m pound Investment, April 30, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Photocopy of article from April 30, 1982 issue of Municipal Journal: 1 page
- Reiss, Charles. "Crossing the Great Divide", January 6, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clipping from The London Evening Standard: 1 page
- Various. Various articles from The Guardian: Home News section, January 12, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clipping, page 4 from The Guardian: 1 page
- Various. Various articles from The Guardian: Futures section, March 22, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clipping, page 36 from The Guardian: 1 page
- Boseley, Sarah. "North Tops Pay League for Standard of Living", March 22, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clipping from The Guardian: 1 page
- Oates, David. "Cornwall Hoping to Halt Years of Economic Decline" also on page "Community Spirit in 190m pound Job Creation Scheme", March 28, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lewis, James. "They Cover the Waterfront", March 28, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clipping from The Guardian: City of Salford section: 2 pages
- Straw, Jack. "Jack Straw Sets Out New Priorities for the Social Rethink: Will Labour be Able to Manage", March 23, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Jacques, Martin. "Dynasty, or how Labour has to Rewrite Mrs Thatcher's Long-Running Role", March 24, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Benn, Tony / Meacher, Michael / Graham, Andrew. "The Real Choice" / "…and the Real Challenge" / "Socialism's Litmus Test", March 28, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clipping from The Guardian: Monday Agenda section: 1 page
- Marquand, David. "Labour Must Break with Labourism to Provide a Socialist Alternative for Britain", March 29, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Tanur, Judith M.. The Trustworthiness of Survey Research. The Chronicle of Higher Education, pp. B1, B2., May 25, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Newspaper clipping: 1 page
- Various. Various Photocopies of Journal Articles 1980-1992, October 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Enterprise Agencies in Longon - A Public Private Sector Partnership?" - David Smallbone
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Enterprise Boards and Some Issues Raised by Taking Equity and Loan Stock in Major Companies" - J. Mawson
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Municipal Enterprise and Popular Planning" - John Palmer
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Local Economic Strategies: Paradigms for a Planned Economy?" - John Benington
- September 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Who Controls Training? - The Rise of the Manpower Services Commission" - Fabian Society
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Attack on Local Government: What it is and What is isn't." -Allan Cochrane
- Summer 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Manufactured in the UK? Special Steels, Motor Vehicles and the Politics of Industrial Decline" - Ray Hudson and David Sadler
- Summer 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Capitalist State and the Local Economy: 'Restructuring for Labour' and Beyond" - Mike Geddes
- July 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Municipal Enterprise, Growth Coalitions and Social Justice" - Phil Cooke
- June 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Regenerating Local Economies" - Tim Crabtree
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Purpose of Local Industrial Policy" - Jamie Gough
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Regional Dimensions of the '1992' Proposals" - Unknown
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "In Search of Equal Partnerships: Prospects for Progressive Urban Policy in the 1990s" - Derek Shearer
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Local State and Local Economic Policy: Political Mobilisation or Economic Regeneration" - Mark Goodwin and Simon Duncan
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Industrial Restructuring and Manufacturing Homework: Immigrant Women in the UK Clothing Industry" - Swasti Mitter
- 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Towards the Unitary State: Tory Attacks on Local Government" - Phil Blackburn
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Industrial Policy and Socialist Strategy: Restructuring and the Unity of the Working Class" - Jamie Gough
- September 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Changing Face of Urban Capitalism" - Book Review Essay - Urban Affairs Quarterly
- March 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Fabian Tract 487 Urban Policy: A New Approach - David Donnison
- July 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Potential and Limitations of Community Businesses in Local Economic Development" - Paul Teague
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The Economics of Local Jobs Plans" - Campbell, Hardy, Healey, Stead, Sutherland
- June 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Economic Development: The Metropolitan Counties 1974-1986" - Andrew Coulson
- June 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "Employment Policy and the Management of Local Economic Strategies" - Norman O'Neill
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  "The New Local Economics: A Reply to John Benington" - Adam Sharples
- Various. Various Government and Planning Organizations Reports, May 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Forwarded report from Chairman Geoff Edge of the West Midlands Economic Development Committee "Direct Investment by West Midlands County Council"
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  "A Proposal for Pension Funds and Other Institutions to Invest in the West Midlands" - West Midlands Enterprise Board Ltd.
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Draft: "Aids to Enterprises: Review and Proposed Strategy" - City of Sheffield: Employment Department
- September 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  "Press Briefing on 1996 Income, Poverty, and Health Insurance Estimates" - Daniel Weinberg, U.S. Census Bureau
- September 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  "Local Economic Developkment in the UK and The USA: Issues for Comparative Study" - The Local Government Centre (paper for Great Lakes Economic Development Conference Responses to Economic Restructuring, Chicago)
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Meyerside Enterprise Board Ltd. informational pamphlet/folder
- Various. Various Government and Planning Organizations Reports - cont'd, December 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Various informational material from The Planning Exchange, Local Economic Development Information Service